It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's a family guy
Hey, Quagmire,
how was your date last night?
Cleveland, it was amazing.
You know what I discovered last night?
- Women have a fourth hole.
- What?
Yeah. I mean, it's only visible if you're
looking from exactly the right angle,
like the entrance to Hogwarts.
But you got to believe that it's there.
Man, I envy you single guys.
No families, partying whenever you want.
These are the only people
I get to party with.
That's where the fourth hole
is, right there.
Right there in the back of the knee.
I like having a family. I got all the crazy
out of my system when I was 18.
Not me. I was dating Lois the whole time.
I never got to be wild.
Except for that time I rode
the mechanical bull at that bar.
Oh, my God, how embarrassing!
Look how much fun I am!
It's like I missed out on half my life.
What I wouldn't give to be 18 again,
like those kids on spring break.
Grim news from Daytona, Florida,
where the remains of
three female college students
were found near a local nightclub.
Reports suggest that
all three were violated sexually
before being brutally murdered.
Oh, man, see that?
Everybody's getting laid but me.
Oh, come on!
Hang on, I'll fix it.
Oh, my God, is he dead?
I think he might be dead!
Oh, did you hear that?
Noah Wyle here thinks he might be dead.
Step aside, junior.
Nope, he's just knocked out.
Damn, I drove all the way out here.
I had to cancel another appointment.
I never like to be too far away
from Mike Wallace.
Hey, Death, I got a favor to ask you.
Could you let me go back in time
and be 18 again?
What, are you high? No.
Coming up next on ESPN,
- Women's Professional...
- All right, you win.
Let's go. But just for one night.
- What the hell? Where are we?
- Oh, my God, this is...
This is Newport Country Club.
I used to be a towel boy here.
That's right, Peter.
You're 18 years old again.
At least, that's how everyone will see you.
Hey, Peter, slap me five.
Slap me ten.
Around the side.
And back again.
Up high.
Down low.
Now, over by the diving board.
Now, on the other side of the pool.
All right, now, I want you to meet me
at this address in an hour,
and we'll slap five there.
- Then afterwards, we'll hit the bars.
- That sounds good to me.
I'm 18, and I'm ready to do some living.
We are gonna raise more hell
than Hellraiser.
Hey, honey, you want
some salt for your steak?
Yeah, sure.
Gotcha! That's more salt than you wanted.
Hello, boys.
Wow, 18-year-old Lois.
Son of a bitch.
I see those ivory lies
in sweet Rosita's eyes
Gonna leave them both behind
when we Tomaso all night
Hi, Peter.
I'm really looking forward to
the movie tonight.
Peter and I are going to see Zapped.
I figured Scott Baio was
androgynous enough
that we could both fantasize about him,
and no one would be gay.
Lois, we got the rest of our lives
for me to not hear a word you just said,
but tonight, I got plans with Cleveland.
But we had a date.
I would eat your poo.
Stay tuned for President Ronald Reagan's
weekly radio address.
Ronald Reagan? The actor?
He's President?
Peter, you're the one from the future.
You should know... Ah, forget it.
Oh, you've got to hear
this new Eddie Murphy cassette I bought.
Hey, did you ever
have a barbecue?
I have!
Wow, you're really good at this game.
Yeah, I've logged a lot of game hours
on Menstrual Miss Pacman.
- What? What?
- Jeez.
- Nothing.
- Bitch.
So, have you seen Ghostbusters?
Save your breath, geekwad.
I'm here with my boyfriend.
You mean that quintessentially '80s guy
with his collar turned up all the way?
- Are you hitting on my girlfriend?
- No, no, I was just being friendly.
I will kick your ass anytime, anywhere.
Okay, how about
top of the World Trade Center,
the morning of September 11th, 2001,
8:00 a. M?
I'll be there.
You think I'll forget, but I won't.
- That was nice.
- I'll say.
Peter, is that... Are you...
- Molly Ringwald?
- Yeah. How's it going?
Wow, you're the biggest star in the
world right now. What are you doing here?
Oh, I like to hook up
with random bar guys.
Lucky for me, huh?
No, a hobby's good.
All right, Peter, your time's up.
- Oh, man, already?
- Yup, come on.
Good to meet you, Molly.
I'll be back later for your career.
- Well, I hope you got your fill, Peter.
- Death, that was totally worth it.
It was even better than the time
I stumbled into
that fat, lonely women's club.
Excuse me, could I get directions
to the Providence Civic Center?
- Do you like cake?
- Yes.
- Do you like my ass?
Do you want to eat cake off my ass?
- What kind of cake?
- Angel food cake.
Well, Rusty, looks like we're gonna
eat our way out of another jam.
- Honey, you awake?
- Morning, sweetie.
Who the hell are you?
What are you doing in my bed?
Peter, it's me, Molly. Your wife?
Molly Ringwald? You're my wife?
We've been married for 20 years.
What's wrong with you?
Hi. I'm Judd Nelson.
I crash here once or twice a week.
Brian, Molly Ringwald is in my bed,
and she says she's my wife!
That's not all.
Look at this place. Everything's different.
This is crazy.
Brian, did you ever see
that Twilight Zone episode?
You know, where the woman wakes up
in the hospital,
and all the doctors are pigs?
- Yeah.
- I like that one.
- But what the hell is going on here?
- You know, I think I have a theory.
It's possible that
when we went back in time,
we somehow altered the past.
Jeez, Brian, that's more ridiculous
than the theory of
why Tom Cruise runs in all his movies.
Wow, that cameraman
has nice, strong arms.
You can't catch me, gay thoughts.
- Hey, where the hell is Lois?
- That's weird.
Looks like she's coming out
of Quagmire's house.
Lois, what the hell?
I'm gone for one night,
and you sleep with Quagmire?
Mr. Griffin, what I do with my husband
is none of your business.
- Husband?
- Morning, Pete.
Hope you and Molly can still join us
for dinner tonight.
Come here, baby. Let's head upstairs
and play hide-and-go-anal.
Brian, what the hell is going on?
We were only in 1984 one night,
and now everything's all messed up.
I think I can explain it to you, Peter.
This line represents
the normal flow of events.
Here's where you met Lois,
here's where you got married,
and here's the present.
And here's the night at the bar.
Now, at some point during that evening,
you did something
that changed the course of your history,
causing the time line to skew off
into an alternate tangent,
where you're married to Molly Ringwald,
Quagmire's married to Lois,
and for some reason,
we have a chalkboard in the living room.
Well, what are we gonna do?
We got to figure out what happened
at this point in time.
And I'll tell you another thing
that worries me.
You ever hear the theory that
if you kill a butterfly in the past,
it can drastically alter the present?
Well, who knows what else we changed.
Tonight,
on The Tonight Show,
movie star, George Clooney.
- Oh, he's good.
Comedian, Dave Chappelle.
He's funny. Like him.
And musician,
Harry Connick Jr.
Wow, what a show.
And now,
ladies and gentlemen, here's...
Chevy!
Oh, God, Brian, we messed up bad.
We messed up real bad.
Howdy, neighbors. Come on in.
Hey, Lois, Peter and Molly are here!
Chris, say hi to Mr. And Mrs. Griffin.
- Hi, Mr. Griffin.
- How's it going, man?
Chris, Stewie!
Oh, my God!
All right, don't freak out, Peter.
Don't freak out like you did
when your goldfish died.
Here you go, Lieutenant Shiny-Sides.
It's okay. You don't have to eat it now.
You're just sleeping. You'll eat it later.
You'll eat it later, Lieutenant Shiny-Sides!
Meg, stop staring at Mr. Griffin.
I'm sorry, Peter.
I'm afraid she's got her father's libido.
What can I say? I'm a Vagitarius. Oh!
- Giggity Giggity Giggity.
Hey, did you guys hear on the news
about President Gore
hunting down and killing
Osama bin Laden with his bare hands?
I know. Who would've thought bin Laden
was hiding out in the cast of Mad TV?
Man, the perfect hiding spot.
The one place no one would look.
Oh, there's the pie.
- Lois, this is a huge mistake.
- What are you talking about, Peter?
You're supposed to be married to me.
We're the ones who were meant to
be together, not you and Quagmire.
It's a little late for that,
don't you think, Peter?
I mean, there was a time
back when we dated
that I thought you might be the one,
but as I recall, you were more
interested in partying with your friends.
Then Glenn came along
and stole my heart.
When he kissed me that night
at the Country Club Dance,
I knew we'd be together forever.
Hey, Lois, I'm ready for your pie.
And you made dessert, too! Oh!
Oh, Glenn, I love all your sex jokes
and your dirty puns.
That's why I married you.
- Let's go upstairs and do it.
- Okay!
Brian, going back in time ruined my life.
We've got to get Death to send us back
to 1984 again, so I can undo what I did.
Or we could just make the best of this.
Al Gore is President.
We could kind of just take that one
and call it a win.
I mean, with Bush, we didn't have
flying cars that run on vegetable oil.
Meet George Jetson
His boy Elroy
Daughter Judy
Jane his wife
Hey, hey, hey! No, no, no, no, no.
I took this one out for you.
You take this one, I keep this!
You are not taking my whole wallet
so you can go shopping.
I was just going to buy some groceries.
Bullshit.
I don't care what it takes, Brian,
I've got to get Lois back somehow.
Well, the only one
who can help us is Death,
and he only shows up
when somebody dies.
That's gonna be tough.
With President Gore's
universal health care,
people are living much longer these days.
And with zero-tolerance gun control
and a strong, well-funded educational
system, there's no street crime.
Face it, Peter, you not marrying Lois
was the best thing
that ever happened to the world.
I don't care. We've got to find a way
to summon Death and quick.
Well, that might do it.
Death! Oh, thank God, you're here!
Listen, you've got to send me
back in time again, so I can marry Lois.
Man, it's been a busy day.
Dick Cheney, the chairman of Halliburton,
shot Supreme Court Justice Scalia
in a hunting accident,
and the bullet went right through him
and killed Karl Rove and Tucker Carlson.
- Oh, my God, Peter, you can't marry Lois.
- I don't know who any of those people are.
All right, hang on. Here we go.
This is the exact moment in 1984
that I sent you to the first time.
You've just got to manage
not to screw it up again.
Lois! Oh, my God, it's so good to see you!
Hey, Peter, you all set
to go see Zapped tonight?
I figured Scott Baio was
androgynous enough that we...
That we could both fantasize about him
and no one would be gay,
yeah, I know the joke.
Hey, you know what?
Listen, Zapped sucks.
Why don't we go see Krull?
- Peter, you know I'm dying to see Zapped.
- I would much prefer Krull.
Well, maybe you should
just go by yourself.
- Well, maybe I will.
- Fine.
Crap. Death!
- What?
- One more time.
Hey, Peter, you all set
to go see Zapped tonight?
I figured Scott Baio was
androgynous enough that we...
That's hilarious! You are a delight.
And Zapped is one of my favorite movies.
I look forward to watching it
with you, sweetheart.
Oh, wonderful.
Death!
Hey, Peter, you all set
to go see Zapped tonight?
- I figured Scott Baio...
- Yes.
Scott Baio, gay, blah, blah, blah, blah.
- I can't wait to see the movie.
- Well, terrific. I'll see you tonight.
Oh, hey, Peter.
Say, I was just getting ready to
hit the town. You want to join me?
I can't, Cleveland, I got a date with Lois.
- It's gonna to be fun.
- It is?
Peter, what the hell are you doing?
You're supposed to be with Lois.
Aw, crap! Death!
No! You know what?
I'm not doing it again.
Screw this. No more mulligans.
You're on your own.
Oh, damn it, Brian,
what the hell am I gonna do now?
I haven't screwed up this bad since
I bought Joe Piscopo that barbell set.
All right, Joe,
now don't get carried away with this.
Don't worry, Peter.
I'll only work out during my downtime.
Oh, look who it is. Only 14 hours late.
If you don't want to spend time
with me, Peter, that's fine.
But at least don't make me
wait up all night for you.
Lois, I'm so sorry.
I promise, I'll make it up to you tonight.
We can watch any stupid movie you want.
- Sorry, I've already got plans.
- What do you mean, "plans"?
I'm going to the Country Club Dance
with Glenn.
I wanted to surprise you
with the invitation last night,
but you never showed up.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to get ready.
Peter, the Country Club Dance is where
Lois said she fell in love with Quagmire.
If they kiss at that dance, you're finished.
You're right, Brian.
We've got to stop them.
And I think I know how.
- Peter!
- Oh, God, sorry! Sorry!
Sorry. You're right, let's go to the dance.
Peter used to be so passionate.
Suddenly, he just doesn't seem
very interested in me anymore.
Lois, if I may speak freely, as a friend,
you deserve better than Peter.
- You deserve a gentleman.
- Oh, Glenn, you're so sweet.
- Oh! Something poked me.
- It's okay, it's okay.
It's just my penis.
Now I know what a TV dinner feels like.
What?
- It's a line from Die Hard.
Hasn't been made yet.
We could write it, Brian.
After we're done with this,
we could write it.
Oh, my God! You just crushed Andy!
- Oh, yeah, sorry about that.
- Oh, oh, you're sorry?
Who's gonna play guitar?
Earth angel, earth angel
Oh, I love this song.
My darling dear
- Lois, may I have this dance?
- Peter, what are you doing here?
I love you, Lois Pewterschmidt.
And not Quagmire, or any man,
she-male, robot or sentient robot
curious about its own existence,
- is gonna keep you from me!
- Peter, I am here with Glenn.
You had your chance with me
and you blew it.
Now, leave us alone.
- Is that what you really want, Lois?
- Yes, it is.
Well, I guess that's it.
Who the hell am I kidding?
I don't deserve her.
Come on, Peter.
Prove to Lois that you love her.
It's your last chance.
Hey, Quagmire.
- Huh?
Sorry, Lois, but I have to do this.
Oh, Peter, that was so passionate.
Why, I didn't know
I meant that much to you.
Are you kidding?
Lois, I couldn't bear to live without you.
I came back thinking
I was missing something in my life,
but what I almost missed was
the best thing that's ever happened to me.
Lois Pewterschmidt, will you be my wife?
Yes. Yes, I will.
Earth angel, earth angel
Please be mine
My darling dear
I'll love you for all time
I'm just a fool
A fool in love with you
I think they want another one.
Uh, okay.
Here's a song by a gay guy.
We're no strangers to love
You know the rules and so do I
A full commitment's what I'm thinking of
You wouldn't get this from any other guy
I just want to tell you how I'm feeling
Got to make you understand
Never gonna give you up
Never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around...
Whoa, whoa, big guy.
You're probably never even
gonna see him again.
Never gonna say good-bye
Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
Hey, Rick, it's your cousin, Marvin.
Marvin Astley.
You know that mediocre,
generic sound you've been looking for?
Well, listen to this!
Never gonna give
Give you up
I didn't like any of that.
Wow, Peter, that's an amazing story.
And I'm touched that you went through
so much trouble just to be with me.
Obviously, I made the right choice
when I married you.
Me, too, Lois.
And, hey, let's just all be grateful
that things are completely
back to normal again.
Who ate all the pecan sandies?
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru